

CONTACT INFO

Winnipeg, MB Canada R2M5S8

ian@imckay.ca

(204) 955-8713

OUALIFICATIONS

Quickbooks Pro Advisor

Xero Certified Advisor

CompTIA A+

Microsoft MTA

TALENTS

Problem solver

Technology enthusiast

Leadership

Time Management

Fast learner

Flexible

Team oriented

Critical thinker

Education

University of Manitoba

Bachelor of Science (Partial)

Completed over 90 credit hours in key areas such as Business, Engineering, and Computer Science. Intend to finish degree when circumstances are more permitting.

IAN MCKAY

CREATIVE AND DRIVEN

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a passionate individual with over 5 years of working experience in accounting, and over 10 years of professional work experience. I have worked directly with clients from a variety of backgrounds - mom and pop shops all the way to C-level executives. This gives me a wide range of experience answering questions and communicating solutions in clear understandable ways. I love technology and have a drive to continue improving myself every way I can.

TECHNICAL SKILL

Xero	Excel/Word/Powerpoint	Zendesk
D	D	
Quickbooks	Google Docs/Sheets	Karbon CRM

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accountant

DAE Enterprises / Nov 2019 - Present

Efficiently completed accounting duties including bookkeeping and processing payroll for a company with over \$3M annual revenue.

- Streamlined accounting procedures to increase productivity
- Transitioned the company to a cloud-based accounting system
- · Prepared financial statements and provided business insights and trends
- Trained owners on a new AR/AP procedure, resulting in reduced workload

Bookkeeping Associate

LiveCA LLP / Aug 2018 - Oct 2019

- Performed bookkeeping and reconciliations in web based software
- · Worked with clients to assure financial data accuracy
- Handled client requests through a support-ticketing system
- Developed bookkeeping workflows and documentation for new and existing clients, including hands on explanations through video calls
- First point of contact for clients and a key factor in client relationship management.

Bookkeeper

DAE Enterprises / Jan 2015 - Jul 2017

Zone Manager

Little Caesars / May 2010 - Dec 2014

- Oversaw operations for two restaurant locations.
- Managed staffing, scheduling, customer satisfaction, cost tracking.
- · Conducted sales performance reviews and financial reporting.
- Managed corporate accounts.
- Created custom reports in order to streamline reporting for our accountants.